Guide to the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980.
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980.
- XI. Speeches and writings.
  - B. Jacob Potofsky. Speeches and Writings. 1918-72.
    - 2. Speeches, articles, and statements.
      - Speech at American Labor Party Rally, October 31, 1940 (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - Remarks on CIO Convention: discusses Murray & Lewis, Lewis & Hillman (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - Speech on "Production of War Needs and Role of Trade Unions," delivered at the Congress of American-Soviet Friendship, November 8, 1942 (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - Unspecified address "Will Unions Come South?" c.1936 (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - Statements - 1940's: end of year address to union members (1941); Labor Day speech (1940); unidentified speech on democracy and the New Deal; "Secretary's Column" possibly written for the Advance (1940); statement on home work c.1936 (Box 173, Folder 5)
      - Notes for speeches - 1940's - includes: "The Liberal Point of View: Who Represents It?"; notes on John L. Lewis; typed notes on ALP; notes on the Amalgamated Insurance Co. (Box 173, Folder 6-8)
      - Speeches - 1945-53: including Statement before House Committee on Labor in support of Amendments to Fair Labor Standards Act, November 9, 1945 (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Statement in connection with the New Republic Round Table in "Next Steps in the Fair Deal", February 16, 1949 (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Address at the NYS CIO Convention, September 10, 1949 (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Address at United Jewish Appeal Dinner for Clothing Industry in Honor of Mrs. Roosevelt, June 15, 1949 (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Address at Twelfth Constitutional Convention of Congress of Industrial Organizations, November 1950 (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Statement on the takeover of "La Prensa", (a newspaper published in Buenos Aires) by Peron. (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Excerpts from speech in Honor of President of Chili (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Speeches - 1951: (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Excerpts from address at dedication ceremonies of the Sidney Hillman Medical Center, Philadelphia. May 5, 1951 (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Statement honoring Hyman Blumberg given at a dinner in honor of his 65th birthday, January 20, 1951 (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Address at International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Milan, Italy, July 9, 1951 (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Speeches - 1952, January to June: (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Statement at Educational Conference concerning "procurement policies of the Pentagon", February 23, 1952 (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Address at Seventh Biennial Convention of the Textile Workers Union of America, April 28, 1952 (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Address at the 18th Biennial Convention of the ACWA, c.1952 (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Address to the 7th Constitutional Convention of the United Furniture Workers, June 1952 (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Speeches - 1952, September - December (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Speech at convention of NYS CIO, May 5, 1952 (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Address at 20th Anniversary Dinner of the Clothing Manufacturers Association of the USA (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Address at 3rd Constitutional Convention of the United Paperworkers of America, CIO (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Address to Local 4 about the Nixon-Stevenson election (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Articles - l952 - including:
      - "Labor's Stake in Migration" (Box 174, Folder 5)
      - Speeches - 1953, January-September, including: statements before House Committee on Education and Labor on Amendments to the Taft-Hartley Act, March 30, 1953 (Box 175, Folder 1)
      - Speeches - 1953, October-December (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - Address at presentation ceremony of Sidney Hillman Foundation award to Harry S. Truman, October 8, 1953 (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - Nominating speech for Walter Reuther, Pres. CIO (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - Speeches - 1954 - January-March (Box 175, Folder 3)
      - Speeches - 1954 - May-September including: (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - Speech at Textile Workers Convention, May 3, 1954 (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - Speech at 40th Anniversary Convention of ACWA (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - Speech "Labor Views the '54 Elections" (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - Speeches - 1954 - October-December (Box 175, Folder 5)
      - 1955 includes: address at celebration of the 80th birthday of Joseph Schlossberg (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - 1956 - January-April includes: address at 20th Biennial Convention of ACWA (Box 176, Folder 2)
      - 1956 - May-December includes: address at the 29th Convention of the ILGWU (Box 176, Folder 3)
      - Statements by Potofsky and Adlai Stevenson concerning the Middle East situation (Box 176, Folder 3)
      - 1957 - January-June includes: speech at NAACP Presentation of Philip Murray Award to President George Meany, May 16, 1957 (Box 176, Folder 4)
      - 1957 - July-December includes: merger resolution between New York State CIO Council and the New York State Federation of Labor, June 24, 1957 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Opening remarks at dinner for George Meany on his appointment to the U.S. delegation to the United Nations, September 24, 1957 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - 1958 - May-August includes: keynote speech at 21st Biennial Convention of ACWA, May 12, 1958 (Box 177, Folder 1)
      - Diary notes from trip to Trade Union Congress and Israel, 1958 (Box 177, Folder 1)
      - 1958 - September-December includes: address at dinner in honor of George M. Harrison, Vice-President of AFL-CIO on the occasion of his appointment to the U.S. Delegation to the U.N., November 25, 1958 (Box 177, Folder 2)
      - Speech at Histadrut luncheon, November 29, 1958 (Box 177, Folder 2)
      - Speeches, 1959 - January-May (Box 177, Folder 3)
      - Speeches - 1959 - June-December includes: (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Speech at testimonial dinner for Louis Simon (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Statement on Glove Workers Resolution (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Statement on Union Label Resolution (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Speech on strike by United Steelworkers of America ("Big Twelve" Steel Companies) (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - 1960 - January-April includes: statement before Committee on Education and Labor in support of a Federal Minimum Wage of $l.25 an hour and extension of coverage of the Fair Labor Standards Act to the Laundry Industries, March 16, 1960 (Box 178, Folder 1)
      - Speeches - 1960 - May includes: (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - Speech "45 Years Amalgamated" (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - Keynote Speech at 22nd Biennial Convention of ACWA, May 30, 1960 (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - Speech "The Challenge to Labor in the Next Ten Years" (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - Speeches - 1960 - June-December includes: (Box 178, Folder 3)
      - Speech at Rally for President-elect John F. Kennedy. October 27, 1960 (Box 178, Folder 3)
      - Speech on 50th Anniversary of union's relation with Hart, Schaffner and Marx, October 29, 1960 (Box 178, Folder 3)
      - Speeches - 1961 - January-March (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - Speeches - 1961 - April-May (Box 178, Folder 5)
      - Speeches - 1961 - June-December includes: Speech at AFL-CIO Convention, December 1961 (Box 179, Folder 1)
      - Speeches - 1962 - February-April includes: Notes on speech on collective bargaining in the clothing industry, February 2, 1962 (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - Speeches - 1962 - May-August includes: Keynote speech at 23rd Biennial Convention of ACWA, May 14,1962 (Box 179, Folder 3)
      - Speeches - 1962 - September-December includes: speech supporting Robert Morgenthau for Governor of New York, October 19, 1962 (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - Address at Hart, Schaffner and Marx 75th Anniversary Dinner, November 27, 1962 (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - Speeches - 1963 - January-March includes: speech on the occasion of the Amalgamated Cooperative Houses 35th Anniversary, March 2, 1963 (Box 179, Folder 5)
      - Speeches - 1963 - April-December includes: speech at ORT Conference (Box 179, Folder 6)
      - Speeches - 1964 - January-June includes: remarks at Laundry Workers Leadership Conference (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Keynote speech (at ACWA Convention) May 11, 1964 (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Speech at NAACP Convention, May 28, 1964 on Civil Rights (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Statement on Immigration Legislation, June 22, 1964 (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Speeches - 1964 - July-December includes: keynote address at 50th Anniversary Convention of ACWA, May 11, 1964 (Box 180, Folder 2)
      - Remarks to retired tailors, August 5, 1964 (Box 180, Folder 2)
      - Speeches to American Club - 1964 - mostly referring to the Johnson-Humphrey ticket. (Box 180, Folder 3)
      - Speeches - 1965 - January-March includes: speech at Histadrut Third Seder, April 18, 1965 (Box 180, Folder 4)
      - Speeches - 1965 - April-July includes: (Box 180, Folder 5)
      - Proceedings from 32nd Convention of ILGWU with statement from JSP (Box 180, Folder 5)
      - Speech at New England Educational Conference (Box 180, Folder 5)
      - Statement on Fair Labor Standards Act Amendments of 1965. July 15, 1965 (Box 180, Folder 5)
      - Speeches - 1965 - August-December (Box 181, Folder 1)
      - Speeches - 1966 - January-April includes: statement on Vietnam, February 18, 1966. (Box 181, Folder 2)
      - Speeches - 1966 - May-September includes: keynote address at 25 Biennial Convention of ACWA, May 23, 1966. (Box 181, Folder 3)
      - Speeches - 1966 - October-December includes: remarks in Chicago on Cooperative Housing, October 27, 1966. (Box 181, Folder 4)
      - Speeches - 1967 (Box 182, Folder 1)
      - Speeches - 1967 - May-August includes: speech at Annual Meeting of United Housing Federation, May 18, 1967. (Box 182, Folder 2)
      - Speech for FDR Memorial, May 30, 1967. (Box 182, Folder 2)
      - Speeches - 1967 - September-December. (Box 182, Folder 3)
      - Speeches - 1968 - March-May includes: Speech at dinner for Willard Wirtz, Secretary of Labor. (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Presentation of Meritorious Public Services Award, March 13, 1968. (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Keynote Speeches, 26th Biennial Convention, May 27, 1968. (Box 183, Folder 2)
      - Speeches - 1968 - August-December includes: statement on Humphrey and Muskie. (Box 183, Folder 3)
      - Remarks at 45th Annual Convention of National Committee for Labor Israel. (Box 183, Folder 3)
      - Speeches - 1969 - January-May includes: speech at Esther Peterson Luncheon, January 16, 1969. (Box 183, Folder 4)
      - Speeches - 1969 - June-December. (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - 1969 Writings - "Ten Years of Progress: A Report on Israel" by AFL-CIO Delegation - George Harrison and Jacob S. Potofsky submitted to George Meany, December 1, 1968. "Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America" (Box 183, Folder 6)
      - Speeches - 1970 - March-May. (Box 184, Folder 1)
      - Speeches - 1970 - August-December includes: testimony before Senate Foreign Relations Committee on war in Indochina, August 13, 1970. (Box 184, Folder 2)
      - Notes on FDR, and Nixon and Vietnam (Box 184, Folder 2)
      - Notice of Bessie Hillman's death in ACWA News. December 27, 1970 (Box 184, Folder 2)
      - Eulogy to Bessie by Potofsky (Box 184, Folder 2)
      - Speeches - 1971 - January - May includes: (Box 184, Folder 3)
      - Speech at 34th Convention of ILGWU. May 12, 1971 (Box 184, Folder 3)
      - Speech at Four Freedoms Award Dinner honoring Senator Muskie. May 20, 1971 (Box 184, Folder 3)
      - Speeches - 1971 - June - December includes: (Box 184, Folder 4)
      - Update report "25 Years Since Hillman's Death" (Box 184, Folder 4)
      - Speeches - 1972 include: (Box 184, Folder 5)
      - Keynote address at 28th Biennial Convention. May 29, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 5)
      - Speeches - 1973 (Box 184, Folder 6)
      - Misc. Writings & Clippings - 1920-1965 includes Yiddish writings (Box 184, Folder 7)
      - Jacob Potofsky's convention programs and other ephemera. 1950-1973 (Box 185-87)
    - 3. Jacob Potofsky oral history interviews.
      - Interview by Neil Gold, July 1964 (Box 188, Folder 1-3)
      - Interview by Kenneth Waltzer (l968) on Origins of the American Labor Party (Box 188, Folder 4)
      - Interview by Elizabeth Balanoff (1970) (Box 188, Folder 5)
      - Jacob Potofsky's draft biography of Sidney Hillman (c.1920) (Box 188, Folder 6-15)
  - C. Speeches and writings by various authors.
    - Speeches and Writings - Joseph Schlossberg and Charles Ervin (Box 189, Folder 1-6)
    - Ervin, Charles "What Really Happened in the Campaign of 1944" (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Hillman, Bessie - 1954-59 (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - Schlossberg, Joseph Statement on the Leopold Morse Injunction, 1916 (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - Schlossberg, Joseph - Speeches - 1920-27 (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - Schlossberg, Joseph - Speeches - 1930-36 includes: "The Court True To Its Anti-Labor Record"; "1936 Olympic Games" (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified (Box 189, Folder 12)
- XII. Press releases.
  - 1922-1943 (Box 190)
  - 1944-1961 and misc., 1936-1943 (Box 191)
- XIII. Financial records and legal papers.
  - A. Financial records.
    - 1914-1915 (balance sheet, July 1, 1915) (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Clothing Workers General Strike Financial Report by Jacob Potofsky - 1916 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Bound volume of expense ledger, 1919-20 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Dunn and Bradstreet Reports on finances of various Clothing Manufacturers - 1935 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Audited ACWA Financial Statements, 1938-44 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Comparative Statement of Stamps Sold, 1936-58 (Box 192, Folder 6-7)
    - Audited Financial Statements, 1944-57 (Box 193, Folder 1-4)
    - Central States Joint Board Financial Statement, 1958 (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Sidney Hillman Foundation Financial Statement, 1955-58 (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - Amalgamated Insurance Fund (Life, Health and Retirement, 1949-60 (Box 194, Folder 1-3)
    - Staff Pension Program, 1936-70 (Box 194, Folder 4-6)
    - Staff Payroll, 1973 (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - B. Legal papers.
    - Sidney Hillman vs. Thomas Rickert (1914) (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - George Suder et al vs. Jacob Riesenberg (Ohio, 1914) (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - M. Sirkin statement re 1914 injunction, Baltimore (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - New York State vs. Isidore Morrison (1916) (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Leopold Morse vs. Sidney Hillman (1917) (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - The People on the complaint of David Wolf against Samuel Stark (1918) (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - The Police Court of the City of Cincinnati against Benjamin Klein et al (1919) (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Excerpt from N.Y. Law Journal. Justice Wagner's Opinion. Rogers Peet vs. Sidney Hillman (1919) (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - Brooklyn Clothing Company vs. ACWA (1919) (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Joseph Michaels (Rochester) vs. Sidney Hillman (1920) (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - J. Friedman (New York) vs. ACWA (1920) (Box 195, Folder 11-12)
    - A.B. Kirschbaum (New York) vs. ACWA (1922) Court Transcript (Box 195, Folder 13-15)
    - Streator, Illinois. Clothing worker affidavit (1922) (Box 195, Folder 16)
    - Joseph Michaels, Morley A. Stern et al against Sidney Hillman individually and as President of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, et al (1920) Transcript of Supreme Court Proceedings (Box 196)
    - Hamilton Tailoring Company vs. Cincinnati Joint Board (1922) (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - International Tailoring Company (Chicago) vs. ACWA (1925) (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous court injunctions, l920's (Boston and Kansas City, Mo.) (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - City of Cleveland vs. Helen Beatey Ames, et al (1937) (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - ACWA vs. Mrs. D.A. Kiser (New York, 1939) (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Clark Manufacturers (Glens Falls, N.Y.) vs. ACWA N.L.R.B. Petition (1957) (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Richmond Brothers (New York) vs. ACWA (1958) (Box 197, Folder 7)
- XIV. Miscellaneous documents.
  - Addams, Jane "Immigrants Under the Quota System" (1929) (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - Advance Resolution signed by Joseph Schlossberg establishing Union newspaper (March 14, 1917) (Box 197, Folder 9)
  - Altschuler and Dreyer of Chicago liquidates (n.d.) (Box 197, Folder 10)
  - Amalgamated Bank of New York. Records and Correspondence
    - 1924-26 includes correspondence with representatives of the Commercial and Industrial Bank of the U.S.S.R. (Box 197, Folder 11-12)
    - 1929-46 includes 1935 confidential report and Jacob Potofsky's correspondence with Bank officers (Box 197, Folder 13-15)
    - Board of Directors Meetings Minutes (1936-39) (Box 198, Folder 1-2)
    - Earnings and Expenses (1938-39) (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee Minutes (1929) (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Financial Statements (1923-46) (Box 198, Folder 5-6)
    - Memoranda and Reports (l923-44) usuary, small loans, health and life insurance, bylaws (Box 198, Folder 7-8)
    - Stockholders Reports (1925-29) (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Press Releases (1923-45) (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Printed Material (including the Union Dollar) and other pamphlet and ephemeral publications (1923-45) (Box 198, Folder 11-12)
    - Clippings (Box 198, Folder 13)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Conventions
    - Nashville, 1914. Endorsements by locals (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Nashville, 1914. Messages and greetings (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Nashville, 1914. Constitution (draft) (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Nashville, 1914. Credentials (Box 199, Folder 3-4)
    - Nashville, l9l4. Proceedings (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Nashville, l9l4. Draft of General Executive Board Report on Convention Proceedings (Box 199, Folder 6-8)
    - Nashville Convention, 1914 (Resolutions) (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - New York Convention, December 26-28, 1914 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Rochester Convention, 1916 (Proceedings) (Box 199, Folder 11-12)
    - Rochester Convention, 1916 (Resolutions) (Box 199, Folder 13-14)
    - Rochester Convention, 1916 (Resolutions) (Box 199a, Folder 1-3)
    - Rochester Convention, 1916 (Telegrams, congratulations) (Box 199a, Folder 4)
    - Baltimore Convention, 1918 (Proceedings, daily summary) (Box 199a, Folder 5)
    - Baltimore Convention, 1918 (Telegrams) (Box 199a, Folder 6-7)
    - 1936 Convention Agenda and Delegates (Box 199a, Folder 8)
    - 1938 Convention (list of delegates, report of Committee on Industrial Organization, daily programs, and finance reports) (Box 199a, Folder 9-21)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers (questions about) n.d. (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Amalgamated Trust and Savings Bank of Chicago
    - Sidney Hillman and Jacob Potofsky's correspondence with Board of Directors, 1923-42 (Box 200, Folder 2-4)
    - Russian American Industrial Corporation (1923-25) (Box 200, Folder 5-6)
    - Financial Statements (1923-48) (Box 200, Folder 7-9)
    - Board of Directors' Meetings Minutes (1933, 1938, 1948) (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Remittances (1923-24) (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Ephemera and clippings (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Corporation for Italy (1949) (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Amalgamated Credit Unions (assets, liabilities, scattered copies of monthly bulletin and correspondence with Credit Union League) 1923-44 (Box 201, Folder 5-7)
  - Amalgamated Housing Corporation
    - Correspondence, 1927-41 (includes correspondence of Jacob Potofsky and Sidney Hillman with Corporation President A.E. Kazan) (Box 201, Folder 8-9)
    - Amalgamated Cooperative Apartments in the Bronx (Press Releases and Progress Reports) 1926-44 (Box 201, Folder 10-12)
    - Our Cooperative House (2lst St) 1920-22 (Box 201, Folder 13)
    - Amalgamated Cooperative Houses in the Bronx (Legal Papers) (Box 201, Folder 14)
    - Amalgamated Cooperative Houses in the Bronx (Printed Material and Clippings) (Box 202, Folder 1-3)
    - Manhattan Amalgamated Dwellings (1930-56) (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Hillman Housing Corporation (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Rochdale and Coop City (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Material including copies of articles by Abraham Kazan and Leon Giovanitti (Box 202, Folder 7-8)
    - Research Department Material collected for 40th and 50th anniversary celebration of the Amalgamated Housing Corporation (Box 203, Folder 1-4)
  - Amalgamated Investors, Inc. (1935-38) (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Amalgamated Security Corp. (1935-39) (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Sidney Hillman's letter to re Trade Union Educational League meeting, November, 1926) (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - American Federation of Labor (includes correspondence with Samuel Gompers re jurisdictional dispute with United Garment Workers) 1914-1936 (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - A.F.L.-C.I.O. Committee on Political Action (cartoons, 1962) (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - American Labor Party (ALP)
    - ALP - General correspondence (1936-38) (Box 203, Folder 11-12)
    - ALP - General correspondence (1944-47) (Box 203, Folder 13-14)
    - Sidney Hillman correspondence (1937-44) (Box 204, Folder l-2)
    - Hyman Blumberg speeches (1944-49) (Box 204, Folder 3-6)
    - Hyman Blumberg personal history (1944) (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - 1936 Constitution, By-laws, Report of the New York State Campaign Director, Mayoral Campaign, Declaration of Principles (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - 1937, 1938 Resolutions, Meeting Minutes (Administrative Committee) (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - 1937-39, ACWA Campaign contributions (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Policy Statement Supreme Court Reorganization (1937) (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - 1938 Campaign Expenses, correspondence of Hyman Blumberg re Dorothy Bellanca's Congressional Campaign (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - 1940 Franklin Roosevelt Campaign. Midwestern Amalgamated Clothing Worker Conference to Help Reelect President Roosevelt. ACWA's letters to Roosevelt (Box 205, Folder 1-2)
    - 1944 Platform and CIO-PAC Campaign in upstate New York (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - American Labor Party State Committee Meeting, April 8, 1944 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - 1944 ALP Split including Fiorello LaGuardia's statement (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - 1944 campaign material (Box 205, Folder 6-8)
    - 1944 Tally Sheets (New York State Campaign) (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - 1943-45, miscellany (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Notes on proposed Municipal Program of the American Labor Party (1944-45) (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Memorandum on Special Congressional Situation (1944) (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - By Laws (1944) (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Executive Board Members (1945) (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Job Applications - Assistant Corporation Counsel (1945) (Box 205, Folder 15)
    - 1945-46 Campaigns (programs and candidates) (Box 205, Folder 16)
    - 1946 Marcantonio-Scottoriggio Case (Press Releases) (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - 1946 Legislative Program (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - 1946 Statement on Foreign Policy (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - 1946 Election Material includes joint statement of American Labor Party, New York Citizen's Political Action Committee and New York State CIO (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - l946 Liberal Party Petitions (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Per Capita tax (l946-47) (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - 1947 (includes statement on Truman Doctrine, Wallace campaign, Taft Hartley Act) (Box 206, Folder 7-11)
    - 1947 Leo Isacson Congressional Campaign (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - 1948-49 (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - Statements including re 5 cent subway fare and Liberal Party Split (Box 206, Folder 14)
    - Financial Statements (1936) (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - Financial Statements (1944-48) (Box 206, Folder 16-17)
    - Press Releases (1936-48) (Box 206, Folder 18-20)
    - Printed and mimeographed campaign material (includes 1945 Legislative Action Bulletin) (Box 207, Folder 1-5)